DR SHAMSUDDEEN ALHASSAN SHUAIBU

08037360129, 07089790635

shamsuddeen alhassan@yahoo.com

CAREER PROFILE:

I am an enthusiastic, experienced and skilled medical doctor, I am also flexible and view challenges as learning opportunities when they arise, fully aware and respectful of professional boundaries and roles. I work effectively as part of a team, with a keen sense of responsibility in and out of leadership positions.

CAREER OBJECTIVES:

To obtain a productive employment with capacity building in a dynamic institution, and to explore capabilities, construct and contribute in accomplishing organizational objectives.

BIODATA:

Date of Birth: 05/9/1992 Nationality: Nigerian Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single

Language Spoken: English and Hausa.

EDUCATION:

Kampala International University, Uganda. Bachelor Degree

MBBS 2012-2017

Ulul-Albab Science Secondary School Katsina, Katsina State, Nigeria.

Senior Secondary School 2008-2011

AACISS Madobi, Kano State, Nigeria.

Junior Secondary School 2005-2008

Yamma Primary School Tudun Wada, Kano State, Nigeria.

Primary School 1998-2004

WORKING EXPERIENCE

HOUSE OFFICER

Federal Medical Centre, Katsina. July 2019- June 2020

MEDICAL OFFICER

Topcare Specialist Hospital Kano (July 2020 – December 2020)

Ameer Clinic and Maternity (August 2020 - December 2020)

A-Razak Clinic and Maternity Kano (December 2021 – Present)

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS (NYSC)

3 Brigade Medical Centre, Bukavu Barracks Kano (January 2021 - November 2021)

PERSONAL AND COMPETENCE SKILLS:

- Good Interpersonal skills
- Ability to work under pressure
- Adaptability
- Flexibility
- Teamwork
- Proficient in the use of Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, and power point.
- Integrity
- Target-oriented

AFFILIATIONS:

- Nigerian Medical Association (NMA)
- Medical and Dental Council of Nigeria (MDCN)
- Uganda Medical and Dental Practitioners council (UMDPC)

HOBBIES:

Watching movies, Travelling, and playing Soccer.

REFEREES:

- •Associate Prof. Ssebuufu Robinson
 Dean faculty of clinical Medicine and Dentistry
 Kampala International University Western Campus, Uganda.
 +256772507248
 rssebuufu@gmail.com
- •Dr Adamu Saminu Adamu Department of Obstetrics And Gynecology Federal Medical Centre, Katsina Adamusaminu1984@gmail.com 08032880636
- •Major (Dr) A.O Okorie Commanding Officer 3 Brigade Medical Centre, Bukavu Barracks Kano. Toniaobby@yahoo.com 08037260265